// Minimum of 10 questions or it crashes the previewer.
// only one js file containing "questions" can be open at once.
const questions = [
 {
     question: "Devenir",
     optionA: "To become",
     optionB: "To come back",
     optionC: "To leave",
     optionD: "To arrive",
     correctOption: "optionA"
 },
 {
  question: "Revenir",
  optionA: "To become",
  optionB: "To come back",
  optionC: "To leave",
  optionD: "To arrive",
  correctOption: "optionB"
},  {
 question: "Partir",
 optionA: "To become",
 optionB: "To come back",
 optionC: "To leave",
 optionD: "To arrive",
 correctOption: "optionC"
},  {
 question: "Arriver",
 optionA: "To become",
 optionB: "To come back",
 optionC: "To leave",
 optionD: "To arrive",
 correctOption: "optionD"
},  {
 question: "Monter",
 optionA: "To go up",
 optionB: "To stay",
 optionC: "To go down",
 optionD: "To die",
 correctOption: "optionA"
},  {
 question: "Rester",
 optionA: "To go up",
 optionB: "To stay",
 optionC: "To go down",
 optionD: "To die",
 correctOption: "optionB"
},  {
 question: "Descendre",
 optionA: "To go up",
 optionB: "To stay",
 optionC: "To go down",
 optionD: "To die",
 correctOption: "optionC"
},  {
 question: "Mourir",
 optionA: "To go up",
 optionB: "To rest",
 optionC: "To go down",
 optionD: "To die",
 correctOption: "optionD"
},  {
 question: "Sortir",
 optionA: "To go out",
 optionB: "To come",
 optionC: "To go home",
 optionD: "To go back",
 correctOption: "optionA"
},  {
 question: "Venir",
 optionA: "To go out",
 optionB: "To come",
 optionC: "To go home",
 optionD: "To go back",
 correctOption: "optionB"
},  {
 question: "Rentrer",
 optionA: "To go out",
 optionB: "To come",
 optionC: "To go home",
 optionD: "To go back",
 correctOption: "optionC"
},
{
 question: "Retourner",
 optionA: "To go out",
 optionB: "To come",
 optionC: "To go home",
 optionD: "To go back",
 correctOption: "optionD"
},
{
 question: "Na√Øtre",
 optionA: "To be born",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To come",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionA"
},
{
 question: "Entrer",
 optionA: "To be born",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To come",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionB"
},
{
 question: "Venir",
 optionA: "To be born",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To come",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionC"
},
{
 question: "Passer",
 optionA: "To be born",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To come",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionD"
},
{
 question: "Tomber",
 optionA: "To fall (to fall down)",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To go",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionA"
},
{
 question: "Tomber",
 optionA: "To fall (to fall down)",
 optionB: "To enter",
 optionC: "To go",
 optionD: "To pass by",
 correctOption: "optionC"
},
]